adpasar.sg 2018-05-09

# Online Shopping Singapore - Shopping site for cheap second hand items & garage sale discounts locally.

**  
Privacy Policy  
**  
  
---  
  
 **adpasar** privacy policy is detailed below, and we ask you to read them thoroughly. We are constantly improving the tools & services you can use to better manage information that you provide to us. Kindly refer to this policy document from time to time to get updated.  
  
 **Policy Coverage**  

This policy applies to this site only and our partners & affiliates have their own privacy policy statements, which we encourage you to read whenever you visit & use their sites or services. When we talk about "adpasar" or "we" in this policy, we are referring to this site itself as well as the company that wholly own and run the site.  
  
 ** Useful Definitions**  

"Personally identifiable information" is information such as your name, birth date, e-mail address, mailing address or some other details that can potentially be used to uniquely identify you as an individual.

Anonymous Information is not personally identifiable information. Anonymous information is information about how you use or iterate with our site (such as sections or pages visited and search keywords used when searching). Anonymous information may include the domain names and/or I.P. addresses (as explained in greater detail below) of browsers that visit our site, time of day the site was visited, and other non-personally identifiable information. Anonymous information is information that is not directly linked to a specific individual but helps to characterize the usage pattern and improve our services.

The next sections will elaborate on how we collect and make use of anonymous information and personally identifiable information.  
  
 **Collection and Usage of Personally Identifiable Information**  
  
 _  
Signing up as new member_

Firstly, we want to assure you that you can visit our site and use many of our available services without informing who you are or revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself to us. **_It is only during registration to become a member will you be requested to provide us with personally identifiable information._**

While most of our tools & services do not require any form of account registration, we do require registration for the use of certain critical services, such as participating in the online auction, making a purchase, or submitting new listings. During this sign-up process, we require you to fill up certain fields, offer optional fields for you to complete, and request you to choose a desired username and password for your own protection. For example, we may ask for contact information (such as full name, email address, and postal code). We will manage and use this contact details in several ways: 

  * to welcome you as the new member of our community & marketplace 

  * to keep you updated about new features and services available through adpasar 

  * to display advertisements on certain pages when they match your interests 

  * to personalize greeting using your name on messages we deliver to you 

  * to share limited details within the close circle of our affiliates and partners

We will save your settings or preferences indicated to us during sign-up and whatever changes that you make thereafter. We promise to respect your preference indicated to us at all time.

 _Lucky draw & Contests_

To bring you more benefit by using our site, we may from time to time organize contests on our site in which we require participants to provide certain contact information, such as their email addresses and mailing addresses). If you participate in these events, your contact information will be used to reach you in connection with the events and the prize to be won. We may also use the collected contact information to send you information about our services, as well as offers tailored to your interests by our affiliates, premium advertisers, and sponsors. You may choose to opt-out of receiving such mailings at any time.

 **Sharing Limited Contact Information Between Users**  
  
To ensure smooth transactions between our members, it is the adpasar policy for members to supply us with a valid contact information at all time. It is also very important for you to be responsive and follow up on the trading transactions done on our site. In the event that your primary contact information is outdated or invalid, or you have failed to respond to member's request to complete a transaction, or in such cases deemed appropriate by us, we may release your secondary contact detail such as phone number to the member who has entered into a trade transaction with you via our system.

Please be assured that only minimum contact information is required (ie. phone number) in this scenario in order to re-establish communication between you and the other member so that pending transaction can be resumed.  
  
 **Sharing Personally Identifiable Information with 3rd Parties**  

To deliver advertising & promotion to you that most closely matches your interests, we share your personal information with carefully selected companies with whom we have relationships and trust. Our partners and affiliates who receive information from us have the right to use the data we provide them (sometimes, in connection with other details they may already have gathered about you), but are generally prohibited from sharing this information with other companies or people externally. 

**PLEASE ALSO NOTE:** In certain special cases & scenarios, we may have to disclose your personally identifiable information when we have strong reason to believe that disclosing this piece of information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to you, or otherwise injuring or interfering with our rights, property, personnel, services or operations, or to other adpasar users, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. We may also disclose your personally identifiable information when we believe the law requires it or in response to demand by law enforcement authorities in connection with a criminal investigation, or civil or administrative authorities in connection with a civil case or investigation.  
  
 **Anonymous Information**  

When you visit or use the services on our site, our system will collect anonymous information, even if you have not registered with us. We use this information to personalize your experience at our site, show you more relevant advertising & promotional messages, and generally to improve our services in future. We share this anonymous information with selected advertisers and partners, including our technology partners in order to deliver to you relevant advertisements and a more pleasant service experience.

We will not share any anonymous information about your use on our site if that information is or will be linked to your personally identifiable information unless you have given us the authorization to do so.  

 **The use of IP Address**  
  
An IP address is a set of numbers that is assigned to your devices whenever you connect to the Internet via your internet service provider. Our web servers - the computers that serve you the web pages for viewing, automatically identify your computer by the IP address during your session online with us.

We may collect IP addresses for purposes of system administration, to report anonymous user information to our advertisers (as explained above), to bring more relevant and better services to you, and to secure the use of our site.

We may use IP addresses to identify users of our site when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our site's policy or to protect our service, site, or other users.  
  
 **Keyword Search & Browsing of Results**  
  
Certain advertisers or sponsors have paid for the right to display advertisements on search results pages corresponding to certain words. For instance, a particular manufacturer may want its advertisement to be displayed when users search for keywords that closely match its products. Other than this, there may also be others common or creative method of advertising offered to our advertisers as well.

To provide better advertising features & services to our advertisers, we have the right to control how the browsing & search results are displayed, organized, and in any sequence deemed fit to us. We will also serve advertisements on the listings that you have submitted through us via our platform.  
  
 **Third-Party Relationships**  

In order to provide you with the most updated news and features that match your interests, adpasar has established long-term relationships with many of the best media and services companies in the market both locally and abroad. You can, therefore, recognize these sites by the joint branding of adpasar and such companies. For example, if you see a logo in the upper-right corner of the page that says 'Powered by adpasar', you will know you are on a co-branded Web page on our partner sites. If you ever have any questions about whether certain information, content or services pertain to us, or are "powered by" one of our partners, please contact us to verify.

Whenever you supply registration information on certain co-branded Web pages or for certain services provided in conjunction with third party partners, we strongly advise you to carefully read the privacy policies provided by or in association with such third parties, and make an informed decision on your own whether or not to continue utilizing the services based upon the privacy policies posted on these co-branded Web pages, at your own discretion.

In addition to finding co-branded Web pages, you may also find direct links on adpasar to the sites offered by third parties. Some of these sites are authorized to use our brand and/or logo. Again, you should make every effort to carefully read these third party privacy policies, and make an informed decision on your own as to whether or not to continue using their sites based upon these sites' privacy practices, at your own discretion. It is important to note that no third-party sites are covered by this Privacy Policy.

 **VERY IMPORTANT:** If you ever feel that a site using the adpasar brand and/or logo has not posted an acceptable privacy policy, or is not following the privacy policy it has posted, please inform us promptly. We will forward complaints to the appropriate third parties to ensure that your concerns are adequately handled. Of course, if any of these third party companies does not have a privacy policy that is acceptable to you, you should refrain from providing information until your concerns have been satisfactorily addressed.

 **Log files**  

Like many other Web sites, adpasar makes use of log files to capture usage information. The information collected inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, name & type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time, referring/exit pages, and clicks count to analyze trends, administer the site, track movement around the site, and gather demographic details. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.  
  
 **Cookies & Web beacons**  

adpasar does use browser cookies to collect & store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize web content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor supplies via their internet browser.  
  
 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**  

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on adpasar.

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to adpasar and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners & affiliates may use browser cookies and web beacons on our site. Our valued advertising partners include: 

Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use advertising technology to serve advertisements and links that appear or adpasar send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your device IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

adpasar has no access to or control over these browser cookies that are used by these third-party advertisers. 

We encourage you to consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices or advertising features. The adpasar privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options on your device. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. **Important:** Disabling cookies on your browser may cause some or all of our services to stop working.   
  
**Security**  

We operate a secure data networks and servers hosted in data centers that are protected by industry standard technology that includes but not limited to firewall, password protection and encrypted channel for our services. We have standard security measures in place to actively protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the data under our control.

We have SOP (Standard Operating Procedure) that govern our daily operations where only authorized employees have access to the information you provide us. For example, we impose strict rules on adpasar employees who have access either to the databases that store user information or to the physical servers that host our services. While we cannot fully guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of data will not occur, we promise to make every effort (such as the use of employee passwords and non-disclosure agreements) to prevent such unfortunate occurrences.  
  
 **Contacting Us**  

If you have questions about this privacy policy or the practices of this site, feel free to contact our helpdesk by using our online contact form on the site itself.
